她回来了 她回家了
She's back! She's home!
菲莉帕回家了
Philippa came home!
两年过去了
Two years,
一切都还和我记忆中一样
and everything looks exactly as I remember.
我以为自己永远不会回来这个地方了
I never thought I would see this place again.
这次我们有18人
There were 18 of us this time.
都是从帝国的各个角落
Culled from every corner of the Empire
被抓到地球参加比赛
and brought to Terra for the contest.
我们被告知 接下来的几年里
We were told that only one of us would survive
我们当中只有一个人能活下来
the years to come.
只有一个孩子
One child
能代表最纯粹的地球血统
the purest expression of the Terran identity.
他们让我们互相残杀
They pitted us against each other.
过了一个又一个月 人数逐渐减少
And month by month, our numbers dwindled.
那 你赢了吗
Did... did you win?
比赛结束了吗
Is it over?
还有两个人活着
Two of us still live.
桑和我
San and me.
我和桑
Me and San.
我们
We are two
双生一体
but one.
直至永远
Forever.
竞赛当中禁止出现“朋友”这个词
The word "friend" was forbidden during the contest,
但我们在别人听不到的时候向对方耳语说出这个词
but we whispered it to each other when no one could hear.
桑和我将我们的技能结合起来
San and I combined our skills
一起对付监察者和其他参赛者
against the proctor and the other contestants.
但你们当中只有一个人能当皇帝
But only one of you could be emperor.
还剩下一个任务
One task remains.
最先完成任务的人就可以统治帝国
The first to complete it rules the Empire,
而另一个人将终生
and the other spends the rest of their life
侍奉新皇
in servitude to the new emperor.
你要做什么
What do you have to do?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你做了什么
What did you do?!
与过去的链接必须斩断
No ties to the old life are permitted.
皇帝只能忠于职责
An emperor can only be loyal to duty.
如此帝国方能强大
Thus does the Empire remain strong.
如此帝国方能兴盛
Thus does it grow.
妈妈       菲莉帕
Mom.    Philippa.
你完成了你的对手无法完成的任务
You succeeded where your competitor could not.
带他过来
Bring him here.
桑缺乏勇气 没有通过最后的试炼
San did not have the strength to pass the final test.
现在 他的村庄燃成灰烬 证明他的软弱
Even now, his village burns as a testament to his cowardice.
我爱你
I love you.
你赢得了比赛
You have won the contest.
宣布你的胜利吧
Claim your victory.
桑  走上前
San, step forward.
现在你的生命只为侍奉于她的足下
You live now only to serve at her heel.
在掌握你生死的皇帝面前跪下
Kneel before the one who owns your life.
我们双生
We are two...
一体
But one.
不再是了
Not anymore.
菲莉帕·乔久万岁
All hail Philippa Georgiou!
皇帝万岁
All hail the emperor!
万岁 万岁 万岁
Hail! Hail! Hail!
万岁
Hail!
我是总控
This is Control
有一条最优先级信息给阿尔法小队领队
with a priority message for Alpha Team Leader.
你的新下属是皇帝菲莉帕·乔久
Your subject is Emperor Philippa Georgiou,
地球帝国前任统治者
former ruler of the Terran Empire.
地球帝国存在于一个平行宇宙
It's in a parallel universe
在所有历史记录中
with the most criminal population
该帝国的臣民最为残暴
in recorded history.
即使在那里 乔久仍能以暴政完全掌控帝国的每个角落
Even there, Georgiou had the market cornered on atrocities.
2257年 她被带到我们的宇宙
In 2257, she was brought to our universe
并加入31区
and joined Section 31,
但几年后 我们失去了联系
but after a few years, we lost contact.
近日 乔久被发现使用假名
Recently, Georgiou was spotted using an alias
出现于联邦领域的边界
in the border territory outside Federation space,
我们正于该边界处追踪黑市上一个新的威胁
where we're tracking a new threat on the black market.
你的小队应在此发挥作用
This is where your team comes in.
联邦条约禁止我们跨过边界
Federation treaty forbids us from crossing over that border,
也就意味着星际舰队不能暗中行事
which means Starfleet cannot get its hands dirty.
你和你31区的队伍将前往联系乔久
You and your 31 team will go in, make contact with Georgiou
发现并控制那个威胁
to help identify and neutralize the threat.
但需注意
But make no mistake
恶犬咬人  多加小心
this dog bites, so watch your backs.
你们有24小时的时间完成这项任务
You have 24 hours to complete the mission.
开工吧
Get to work.
杜·弗朗克女士
Madame du Franc?
蜜月套房里出了个小事故
Small incident in the honeymoon suite.
新娘似乎是快到高潮的时候
I'm afraid the bride molted
蜕皮了
just as things were coming to a climax.
维吉尔 说重点
Virgil,get to the point.
我派出了一支生化小队 并致以你的吊唁
I sent a biohazard team and your condolences.
还有 有一位顾客想和你说句话
Also, there's a customer hoping for a word with you.
他看起来很清醒 但已经喝了不少
He seems entirely sober but quite intoxicating.
维罗妮克·杜·弗朗克女士同意见你
Madame Veronique du Franc will see you.
阿洛克·萨哈  这位是维罗妮克·杜·弗朗克女士
Alok Sahar, Madame Veronique du Franc.
杜·弗朗克女士通常要预约才能谈生意
Madame du Franc normally does business by appointment.
那我想预约一下
I'd like to make an appointment.
噢 这位绅士想预约一下
Oh, the gentleman would like to make an appointment.
现在就预约   现在就预约 女士
Now.        Now, madame.
（法语）不可能      不可能
Impossible.           Impossible.
再见 维吉尔
Au revoir, Virgil.
这玩意儿是非法的
That is illegal.
能赚钱
And that makes money.
我这里是声誉良好的生意场所
This is a reputable establishment.
据我所知可不是这样
Not what I heard.
我们为什么不去你的办公室讨论呢
Why don't we discuss it in your office?
我为什么要带你去我的办公室呢 阿洛克·萨哈
Why would I take you to my office, Alok Sahar?
因为这玩意儿得自己试试
Because it's a hands-on experience.
我所到之处
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
人尽皆知
♪ Everybody knows... ♪
悦耳蓟
注：应该是某种植物
Dulcet thistle.
悦耳蓟已经灭绝了
Dulcet thistle's extinct.
我有很多存货
I've got a dozen keys of this stuff.
你要来点吗
Have you partaken?
这将是我少有的第一次尝试新东西
This would be one of my few first times.
来一杯潘趣酒
Packs a punch.
快乐的一杯
A happy punch.
干杯
Bottoms up.
敬赚钱             敬你
To money.      To you.
现在 我们别说废话了
Now, let's cut the shit.
31区来我的空间站干什么
What is Section 31 doing in my space station?
你觉得我会认不出来一个特工吗
Hmm? You think I don't know an agent when I see one?
你带领着一个6人组成的小队
You're heading up a team of six operatives,
他们分散在这个酒吧里
and they're all over the bar.
有一个查莫人
There's the Chameloid,
一个绿血变形人
a green-blooded shape-shifter,
试图与一个德尔塔人调情寻欢
trying to muster sexy time with a Deltan,
多么甜蜜的人形陷阱
a walking honey trap
31区用来转移注意力的惯用伎俩
31's obviously using as a distraction.
可实际上查莫人是银河系里唯一
Except Chameloids are the only species in the galaxy
对德尔塔人的魅惑能力保持免疫的种族
immune to Deltan sexy time charm.
然后是那个穿着一身高端器械的家伙
Then there's the guy with all the high-end mech,
傻站在后面 显得好像他有脑子似的
standing in the back, looking like he has thoughts.
机械生命 有的可不只是蛮力
Mech life, it ain't just about the brute force.
我的意思是 他显然更头脑简单 四肢发达
GEORGIOU:
I'm gonna say heavy on artillery, low on IQ.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
以及某个我们可不能忘了的瓦肯人
And we can't forget the Vulcan,
被舞台表演逗得哈哈大笑
laughing way too hard at the stage banter.
鉴于瓦肯人从来不笑 他要么也是个白痴
And since Vulcans never laugh, he's either an idiot, too,
要么就是在庞发期间脑子变得不正常了
or lost his mind during pon farr and went insane.
哦 别这样 那很好笑啊
Oh, come on. That was funny.
还有那个在一旁呛他嘴的一脸严肃的人类
GEORGIOU:
And the very serious human you stuck him with...
你控制一下自己
Reel it in anytime.
她看着就是一副苦大仇深的样子
...she's got a stick so far up her backside,
一开口就能听出来
it's coming out her mouth.
冷静一点
Just reel it in.
那是
That would be
加勒特上尉
- Lieutenant Garrett. - Mmm.
星际舰队的
Starfleet.
无趣到死
Where fun goes to die.
你找我花了不少时间啊
It took you long enough to find me.
只要你留在巴拉姆空间站
We knew that having you here on the Baraam
对我们来说 总有一天会派上用场
would be valuable to us one day.
好吧 我不得不说我一点儿也不感动
Well, I'm not feeling motivated to be valuable
我确实很有用 不过只为我自己所用
to anyone but myself.
今夜请说愿意（没找到这歌叫什么名）
♪ Say yes tonight ♪
一切都可应允
♪ Say yes to everything... ♪
所以 我们就这么开始谈判？
So, is this where we start negotiating?
这取决于
Hmm, that depends.
你们什么时候知道我的?
How long have you known about me?
从你自前任站主那儿接手开始 我们就知道了（不太确定这个owner指谁）
Ever since you took over from the previous owner,
但我们还没能找到这个人
who we still haven't found.
好吧 之前所有的都没找到
Well, all of.
-这可不是我干的 -乔久皇帝
- That wasn't me. - Emperor Georgiou,
我完全有权逮捕你
I am authorized to arrest you
抹除你的意识
and wipe your mind clean.
但是话又说回来 我心里还是觉得
But then again, there's a part of me
你有记忆的活着比较好
that wants you to live with your memories.
尤其是那些关于种族灭绝的记忆
The genocidal ones.
你有权逮捕我
Being authorized to arrest me
不等于你有能力逮捕我
isn't the same as being able to arrest me.
你真的希望31区 希望我
You really want Section 31-- want me--
不止不休地追着你吗？
dogging you until the end of time?
无聊
Boring.
往事如影随形啊
The past always catches up with you.
以及 我知道我们都讨厌这一点
And as much as both of us
但我会帮你个忙
might hate it, I'm doing you a favor.
最后一次任务
One last mission.
听着
Listen.
你相信命运吗?
Do you believe in fate?
我信
Because I do.
你无处可逃
You can't hide from it.
你在这里什么都不是 乔久
You're nothing here, Georgiou.
但我给你一个机会
I'm giving you a chance to get back in.
参与这场跨银河系的行动
In on the action on a galactic scale.
不要逃避这一点
Stop running from it.
做你自己
Be who you are.
或者就在这个酒吧待一辈子
Or stay and tend bar for eternity.
我们着手行动吧
Let's get on with it.
菲莉帕·乔久 认识一下我的团队
ALOK: Philippa Georgiou, meet my team.
这是梅尔
This is Melle.
泽弗
Zeph.
你看起来像一把瑞士军刀
You look like a Swiss Army knife.
等等
Uh, hold on.
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means, but I'm not gonna
但我不可能傻站在这里被你侮辱
just stand here and get insulted.
我没说你
I'm not talking about you.
我是说你的装备
I'm talking about your suit.
鉴于你是新来的
ZEPH: Um, you're new,
所以我就解释这一回
so I'm gonna just explain this one time
当你在说装备
that when you are talking about the suit,
你就是在说我
you're talking about Zeph.
泽弗有点
- Oh. - QUASI: Zeph suffers from
机械变形障碍症 大概
what we call mecha dysmorphia.
我也许不知道那是啥意思
ZEPH: And I may not know what that is,
但我也不接受
but I'm also not gonna take that
夸西 我觉得你冒犯了我
from you, Quas, and personally I'm offended.
我觉得你应当知道 -这挺对的
- I think you should know... - Well, it's accurate.
你不能诊断我得了什么 你不是医生
It's not a diagnosis. You're not a doctor.
泽弗 泽弗 泽弗
ALOK: Zeph. Zeph, Zeph!
-他知道 他知道 他知道 -好吧
- He knows. He knows. He knows. - Okay, fine.
他知道
He knows.
-他明白的 他明白的 -是的
- He gets it. He gets it. - Yes.
好吧 那个瓦肯人是怎么回事？
Okay, what about that Vulcan?
没人跟她说吗？
Nobody told her?
这个？正跟你说话的这个东西？
This? The thing you're talking to?
这个瓦肯外表不过是台机器
The Vulcan's just a machine.
我在里面
I'm inside.
驾驶它
Driving.
我通过体内的备用驾驶舱控制这具身体
I control the body from a backup vehicle.
没错，就是我用来在一些狭窄空间里进出的玩意儿
Yeah, something I use to get into tight spots.
你好啊
Hi there.
我是法兹
I'm Fuzz.
法兹是纳米人
Fuzz is a Nanokin.
一个天性爱玩的家伙
Real fun-loving guy.
你好
Hello.
直到他不感兴趣了
Except for when he's not.
然后他就会变成个有被管抵触狂躁症的家伙
Then he's deranged with an anger management problem.
你只说第一句就行了 夸西
Well, you could've stopped at the first thing, Quasi.
一个非法制造的瓦肯型运输载体
A bootleg Vulcan conveyance?
你肯定在黑市上见过不少了不得的东西
You must see cool stuff on the black market.
纳米人都是天生的拾荒者
QUASI: Nanokins are pretty scavengery.
31区在废弃的船只上
31 made first contact when
发现了虫害，然后才有了第一次接触
we discovered an infestation on a derelict ship.
-夸西 - 啊糟了
- Quasi. - Oh, shit.
你再说一遍“虫害”试试看 夸西
Say "infestation" one more time, Quasi.
你应该说“拾荒者” 你这袋没形状的烟灰
Say "scavenger," you sack of amorphous soot!
我...我一顺口就说出来了
I-I s-- I heard it as soon as I said it.
我会猛踹你的屁股
I will kick your ass
直到你变成一团液体的……
until you cannot form a solid mass of...
法兹 法兹 控制一下
Fuzz. Fuzz. Lock it down.
我已经控制了
I am locked down.
我被困在一个巨大的瓦肯机器脑袋里
I'm trapped inside a giant robot Vulcan head.
没人比我还受控了
No one is more locked down than me right now!
纳米人情绪光谱不太稳定
Nanokins have a wonky emotional spectrum.
不不不不 别想
No, no, no, no, no, no, I will not
用居高临下的态度对我 梅尔
be condescended to, Melle,
尤其是你 因为说实话
particularly not by you, because honest...
我爱你 你就是一切
I love you. You are everything.
-我的光谱感应对你有用吗？-法兹
- Does my spectrum work for you? - ZEPH (echoing): Fuzz.
我意思是 就像是 你认真的吗或者……-法兹
- I mean, like, like,are you into it or...- Fuzz!
法兹
Fuzz!
她在侮辱你 朋友
She's insulting you, pal.
我就知道德尔塔人又会做他们德尔塔人的那一套
I know Deltans are gonna do their Deltan thing,
但是自尊自爱点吧 伙计
but have a little self-respect, would you?
我们能继续吗？
Can we continue?
然后这是瑞秋·加勒特上尉
And that's Lieutenant Rachel Garrett.
只因为这个任务被派遣到31区
She is detailed to Section 31 for this one mission only.
你得罪了什么人才被派来这个秘密组织，上尉？
Who did you piss off to get stuck in black ops, Lieutenant?
星际舰队的目标是确保我们行事合规
Starfleet is here to make sure we color inside the lines.
星际舰队的目标是保卫联邦
GARRETT:
Starfleet is here to defend the Federation,
维持和平状态并确保没有人被谋杀
keep the peace and make sure no one commits murder.
-你呢？-等一下
- And you? - One moment.
我认识夸西是因为
ALOK: Quasi came on my radar
他证明了神经胶质细胞簇的存在
when he proved the existence of glioclusters.
神经胶质细胞簇只存在于理论中
Glioclusters are theoretical.
曾经是
Formerly theoretical.
生命充满无限可能
Life is just branching possibilities.
它们以你能想象的任何方式盛开
You know, they bloom and blossom any way you can imagine.
比如 我现在可能会被你吓倒
For example, I could be intimidated by you right now.
毕竟你杀了
I mean, after all, you've murdered
那么多人
so many people...
你好像能看透我的本质
and you seem to be staring right into my soul.
我可以对此做出回应
I could respond to that
或者我可以观察我的感受
or I could observe my feelings right now,
不管它 只做我需要做的事
lock it away and do what I need to do.
-或者 -夸西 选一个吧
- Or... - Quas. Pick one. Hmm?
-是的 -有时夸西能看到太多可能性
- QUASI: Yes. - MELLE: Sometimes Quasi sees
-以至于他的思维可能会有所停滞-谢谢你 梅尔
- so many options he gets brain-freeze.- Thank you, Melle.
-夸西 我们能继续了吗？
- Quasi, can we carry on, please? - Mm-hmm.
我们的目标是达达·诺尔
Our target's name is Dada Noe.
一个有道德底线在哪都存疑的家伙
Dubious moral compass.
在他叛变之前，他在瓦特殖民地经营了一个病理学实验室
Ran a pathology lab on the Watt Colonies before he went rogue.
自此之后 他一直致力于设计生物武器
Since then, he's been designing bioweapons on spec.
诺尔前往巴拉姆空间站是为了
Noe's on his way to the Baraam to sell his latest creation
把他的最新发明出手给米诺斯最高议会
to the Minosian High Council.
米诺斯（不太懂）没有正式的敌对行动
There are no formal hostilities with the Minosian Sway,
当他们拿到这件武器 情况可能会
but that could change if they get their hands
发生变化
on a superweapon.
我们知道这个超级生物武器是什么吗？
GEORGIOU:
Do we know what this bio superweapon is?
不知道 但是我们不能让达达·诺尔出售它
GARRETT:
No, but if Dada Noe is selling it, it's bad.
所以你的任务目标就是确保交易不会发生
So you're here to make sure the sale never happens.
怎么做？
How?
你对我们行动的发觉确实造成了一些影响
Things went south when you spotted us,
但计划仍然可靠
but the plan is still solid.
首先 阿洛克会
First, Alok was going to...
你可以告诉她
You can say it.
和你
Connect.
接触
With you.
-欢迎
- Welcome! Mmm. - Yes.
这点子挺可爱
What a cute idea.
一旦我们适当的分散了你的注意力
Once we had you suitably distracted,
夸西会做另一件事
Quasi would do the other thing Quasi does.
好了 夸西
ALOK: Okay, Quasi.
-麻烦你了 - 好的
- If you would do the honors. - Absolutely.
我们开始吧
Let's get to work.
欢迎欢迎 达达·诺尔
Welcome, Dada Noe.
这时候法兹会参与进来
ALOK: This is where Fuzz comes in.
你绝对想不到我能进入多小的地方
FUZZ:
You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
比如，身体改造组件的内部空间
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
一旦我进入其中
Oh, once I fly inside Dada's body mod,
这就是我要发挥作用的时刻
well, then it's time to get to work.
这么多电路
So many circuits.
太多可能出错的东西了
So many things that could go wrong.
我们这位全副武装的十字军战士
Competency crusader here will talk me through
会通过植入物跟我交谈
the tech on the implant.
如果我认为我们通过达达·诺尔的植入物
And if I think we're putting Dada Noe's life in danger
让他生命垂危
by tinkering with that implant,
我会通过星际舰队
I will unleash the full weight of Starfleet
对此次任务施压
on this whole operation.
嘿 我们讨论的可是一个要出售超级武器的家伙
Oy, we're talking about a bloke who's selling superweapons
他会把东西卖给任何有拉蒂金卡的三流恐怖分子
to any third-rate terrorist with a Latinum card.
听仔细了 满脑子废品的家伙
GARRETT: Listen carefully, Junkyard.
星际舰队不执行暗杀任务
Starfleet does not do assassinations.
唉 别再满脑子的惦记着你的最高指导原则了
Ay, don't get your prime directives in a bunch.
这不会脏了你的手
You are not going to get your hands dirty
也不会让你当不了舰长
and mess up your chances of becoming captain.
我是首屈一指的科学官
I'm a top-tier science officer.
（……我真的不知道怎么处理这两句话……）
- Butt pretzel. - Tight-ass.
太不尊重人了
So disrespectful.
只要加勒特和法兹切断了链接
Soon as Garrett and Fuzz sever that link...
他就会处于我们的控制之下 我会和泽弗一起
...he'll be under our control, and I'll take him down
制服他
- with the help of Zeph. - Mm.
-我是说打他一下 --打一下
- That's what I call a hit. - One.
达达·诺尔会被拘留 他的病原体会被没收
Dada Noe and his pathogen will be in custody
这一切会在卖家出现在巴拉姆空间站之前就完成
before the buyers can even show up to the Baraam.
速战速决
And we are in and out.
呃
Mm. Meh.
OTHERS: Meh?
我有个更简单的计划
I have a simpler idea.
表情很绝望 我看的出来（这歌叫My Domain，歌词翻译是照着网易云的歌词翻译写的）
♪ Desperate, I can tell ♪
所有的祈求
♪ All that begging ♪
都像是为你量身定做的
♪ Suits you well. ♪
现在打爆我的手机
♪ Blowing up my phone now ♪
我向上 你低头
♪ Going up, you bow down ♪
看看是谁需要谁
♪ Look at who needs who... ♪
欢迎欢迎 达达·诺尔先生
Welcome, Monsieur Dada Noe.
您的到来使巴拉姆空间站蓬荜生辉
We're honored to have you here at the Baraam.
我是维罗妮卡·杜·弗朗克 这里的店主
I am Veronique du Franc, the proprietor.
我跟他们讲了准备好我的箱子
I told them to have my suite ready.
是的 先生
Mais oui, monsieur.
我可以送您回房间吗？
May I escort you to your quarters?
请跟我来
Come.
我们有最好的……
We have the most exquisite...
我简直不敢相信你会信任这个反社会的疯子
I can't believe you're trusting this sociopath.
上尉
Well, Lieutenant,
你做好自己的事
you got to do what you got to do,
我知道怎么跟反社会疯子打交道
and I'm kind of familiar with sociopaths.
我说了别带我来
I said don't bring me.
我想您的旅程一切顺利 先生
I trust your trip was without incident, monsieur.
你的团队倒是帮我把一切都打点好了
Well, your people made everything easy.
我们的荣幸 我们到了
Our pleasure. Here we are.
太俗气了
So tacky.
但我想这就是你出名的地方
But I guess that's what you're known for.
这是什么？
What's this?
这东西叫相位转移器
It's called a phase pod.
我的某位客户送给我的礼物
A client of mine gave it to me as a gift,
我自己也有一个
and I got one for myself, too.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
宇宙中的一切
Everything in the universe vibrates
都以特定的波长振动
on a certain wavelength.
该死
Damn it.
把箱子还给我
Give me back my case.
我拒绝
No.
维修费从你的押金里出
That's coming out of your security deposit.
相位转移器则会改变
The phase pod changes the wavelength
接触到的任何东西的物质波长
of whatever they touch.
我和你不在同一相位 你也不和我在同一相位
I am out of phase with you, and you're out of phase with me.
但是我 跟你的箱子在同一相位
I am, however, in phase with your case.
然后我会把它拿走
And I will be taking it with me.
你根本不知道你挑起了什么
You have no idea what you've started.
哎呀
Whoopsie.
印象深刻
Impressive.
你确定你是人类？
Are you sure you're human?
多数时候是
Most days.
谢谢你
Thank you.
把箱子给我
Give me the case.
你是谁
Who are you?
他从那儿走了 那儿那儿 那边
He went that way. That way, that way, that way, that way!
哦 外星人
Oh, aliens.
-裸体外星人 -泽弗 快走
- Naked aliens. - ALOK: Go, Zeph, go.
他往休息室去了 天哪 他们走得真快
He's headed to the lounge. Man, they're moving fast.
梅尔 他朝你来了
Melle, he's coming to you.
哎呀
Yikes.
没事没事
No, it's okay.
-我没事 -梅尔 你看到他了吗？
- I'm all right. - Melle, you got him?
看到了
Got him.
哎呀
Ooh-la-la!
嗨 亲爱的
Ay, amor.
不可能
That's not possible.
它已经被我销毁了
I had that destroyed.
不 不
No. No!
这不可能
It's not possible.
你知道那件武器
You knew that weapon.
是什么武器
What is it?
那是什么武器
好吧 那就来硬的
Fine. The hard way.
永恒的祈求者恳请觐见
The Eternal Supplicant begs approach.
准了
You have my permission.
向女王陛下致敬
All hail Her Most Imperial Majesty,
祖国之母
Mother of the Fatherland,
-瓦肯的君主 -这是什么
- Overlord of Vulc-- - What is it?
它完成了 陛下
It is finished, Your Majesty.
我的工程师们在哪
Where are my engineers?
他们 他们在完工后结束了自己的生命
They... they took their own lives upon completion.
你在为谁流泪 桑
Who is the tear for, San?
说
Speak.
是为您 陛下
It is for you, Majesty.
这都是
It is all...
为了您
...for you.
我再问你 桑
I asked you a question, San.
你为何为我而哭
Why do you cry for me?
看着我
Look at me.
你还记得我们是谁吗
Do you remember who we were?
在这一切之前
Before all this.
好奇的男孩
The curious boy.
天真的女孩
The innocent girl.
我只记得我的失败 陛下
I only remember my failure, Majesty.
别对我撒谎
Don't lie to me.
我们是唯一能理解活着的代价的人
We were the only ones who could understand the cost to stay alive.
我们是一个集体
We made a team.
我们彼此需要 不是吗
We needed each other, didn't we?
我们说过什么 携手共同生存下去
What did we say to carry each other through,to survive together?
我们虽为两人
We are two...
但为一体
But one.
我们虽为两人 但为一体
We are two but one.
如果我说
If I said then,
”我们逃跑吧
"Let's run away,
让我们逃离这场竞争
"let's flee this competition
以及把我们和人族联系在一起的一切“
and everything that binds us to Terra,"
你会说
什么what would you have said?
您问这个问题的时机比您认为的更具诗意
The timing of your question is more poetic than you know.
我会说 好
I would have said yes.
当时
Then.
那么现在呢
But now?
您本可以在您治下创造一些美丽的东西
You could have made something beautiful with your reign.
但是 您却选择了创造这个
Instead, you chose to build this.
这意味着我认识的那个天真的女孩
That means that innocent girl I knew,
她已经
she has been...
被谋杀了
...murdered.
怎么回事
What is this?
你
You...
你服用了一样的毒药？
You took the same poison?
不 我不许你死
No! I forbid you to die!
没有人愿意活在
No one wants to live
您的世界中 皇帝
in your world, Emperor.
你是个怪物
You are a monster!
这是什么令人愉快的地方
And what delightful place is this?
一个安全屋
A safe house.
但对你而言也许不是
But maybe not so safe for you.
你是31区的
You are Section 31.
你为什么不拷问我以获取答案
Why aren't you torturing answers out of me?
你是个暴君
You're a tyrant.
货真价实的
A real one.
折磨你不会有什么用的
Torture wouldn't work.
你怎么会这么了解我这种人
How do you know so much about people like me?
你在某个地方精神体验到了暴政 而且很体验的深刻
You learned tyranny somewhere, and you learned hard.
如果你必须要隐藏这点的话 这是个弱点
If you have to hide it, that's a weakness.
而且我不能有这样的搭档
And I can't have that in a partner.
-我们不是搭档 -不是？
- We're not partners. - No?
我可帮了大忙了
I've been very helpful.
你的计划行不通
You had a plan that couldn't work.
而我给了你更好的
I gave you a better one.
你让我尝到了甜头
You gave me a taste of the action,
知道我还想要更多
knowing I'd want more.
你需要我
You need me.
你选择了我
You chose me.
为什么呢
Why?
不管你认为你的任务是什么
Whatever you believed your mission was,
这远比你想象的更糟糕
it's worse than you thought.
数十亿人的生命危在旦夕 且时间紧迫
Billions of lives are at stake, and time is short.
你先让我了解你 我才能告诉你
Tell me you, and I will tell you me.
唯一可行的办法就是让我知道我在和谁打交道
The only way this works is if I know exactly who I'm dealing with.
我也不属于这个时代
I'm not from this time, either.
我出生于地球 20世纪
I was born on Earth, 20th century.
你已经350岁了
You are 350 years old?
差不多
More or less.
大部分时间我是睡过去的
I slept most of that time.
在我被流放之后
After my exile.
优生战争
The Eugenics Wars.
强化人
Augments...
夺走了我的星球
took my planet.
我的家乡
My home.
我们大概有十个人参加了战争
There was maybe ten of us who fought.
我认识的人不是挨了一枪就是挨了一刀
Everyone I knew either took a bullet or a blade.
我也还以颜色
But I gave some back.
这让她注意到了我
She noticed me.
那个屠杀我家人的强化人
The Augment who slaughtered my family.
他们叫她被标记的吉里
They called her Giri the Marked.
她收留了我
She took me in.
让我比任何人类都强大
Made me stronger than any human should be.
她把我撕成碎片
She ripped me apart
然后把我重塑成了她军队里的又一个强化人
and turned me into another Augment for her army.
我做了很多可怕的事
And I did terrible things.
都是为了像你这样的怪物
All for a monster like you.
因为对于暴君来说 永远只有一个选择
Because for tyrants, there is only one choice:
杀戮
murder.
你还没杀我
You haven't killed me.
暂时还没
Yet.
我能认出那个武器是因为我下令造了它
I recognized the weapon because I ordered it to be built.
召集你的人手
Gather your people.
我们将需要他们每个人
We're gonna need every one of them.
在我的宇宙里 总有阴谋家存在
In my universe, there were always plotters.
总有政变
Always a coup.
所以我造了一件武器来终结所有威胁
So I built a weapon to end all threats.
我称之为天赐之物
I called it the Godsend.
它会引发一种连锁反应
It triggers a chain reaction,
就像病毒一样在群星间传播
like a virus passing between planets.
所到之处 一切都将化为灰烬
Everything in its path incinerates.
整个象限都会消失
An entire quadrant would be lost.
如果我的敌人设法杀了我
If my enemies managed to kill me,
他们就没有什么可统治的了
there would be nothing left to rule.
有个小问题
Yeah, hi. Quick question.
对不起
Sorry.
就一个很小很小的问题
Yeah, no. Uh, just a qu-- it's just a quick one.
这是天赐之物还是天赐之暮
Is it Godsend or God's End?
天赐之物还是天赐之暮
Godsend or God's End?
我不明白你说的有什么区别
I don't hear a difference in what you're saying.
真的？真的？天赐之 物 天赐之 暮
Really? Really? Godsend. God's End.
-我还是没明白 -天赐之物是
- Yeah, I'm still not getting it. - The Godsend is...
等等 天赐之物 我现在听清楚了
Wait, Godsend. I hear it now.
-天赐之物 不是暮 -物
- It's Godsend. No apostrophe. - Send.
天赐之物现在就在这里
The Godsend is here.
怎么来的 那可是另一个宇宙
How? It's from another universe.
我不知道 但是那个人现在持有它
I don't know, but that man had it.
你以为是达达·诺伊的那个人
The one that you think is Dada Noe.
我们都知道是达达·诺伊的那个人
The one we know is Dada Noe.
不 他不是你们的达达·诺伊 不可能是
No, he's not your Dada Noe. He can't be.
他来自人族帝国 是他把天赐之物带来这里
He's from the Terran Empire, and he brought the Godsend here.
只有这样他才会知道那是什么
That's the only way he can know about it.
一旦我们把他关得严严实实
And since we have him locked up tight,
-我要亲自审讯他 -不 不 不
- I'll interrogate him. -No, no, no.
-我们不能相信这个女人说的话 -是啊
- We cannot trust a single word this woman says. - Yeah.
她害我们失去了梅尔
She cost us Melle.
只有她知道我们面对的是什么人
She's the only one who knows what we're dealing with.
是啊 她是这么说的 小兄弟
Yeah, well, so she says, little bro.
小？
Little?
这是身材羞辱
Scale-shamer!
微生物比恐龙更长寿
Microbes outlasted dinosaurs!
冷静点 我要说的是
Calm your boots. What I'm saying is...
我要尿在你的装甲上 直到你全身生锈
I will piss in your suit until you go all rusty like!
这一切都是她搞砸的
...that she's the reason this is all bollixed up.
她是梅尔死的原因 她也是
She's the reason Melle's dead, and she's the reason
我们现在在银河系尽头的原因
we're in the ass end of the galaxy.
听着
Listen up.
乔久和我回船上去
Georgiou and I are gonna go back to the ship.
达达·诺伊是我们与天赐之物的唯一联系
Dada Noe is our only link to the Godsend,
所以我们要找他谈谈
so we're gonna have a little chat with him.
什么
What?
她叫菲利帕·乔久
Her name is Philippa Georgiou,
女王陛下
Her Most Imperial Majesty.
祖国之母
Mother of the Fatherland.
瓦肯的君王
Overlord of Vulcan.
克罗诺斯的主宰 安多利亚的女王
Dominus of Qo'noS, Regina Andor,
菲利帕·乔久·奥古斯都·伊波尼亚斯·塞塔瑞斯
Philippa Georgiou Augustus Iaponius Centarius.
酷
Cool.
配薯条的吗
That come with fries?
很好笑 对吧
That was good, right?
好吧
Okay.
每次你不直接回答她的问题
Every time you don't answer her questions directly,
女王陛下就会狠狠地打你的脸
Her Majesty will punch you in your face.
好吧
Fine.
我是达达
I'm Dada.
达达·诺伊 先念达达 再是诺伊
Dada Noe. Just Dada, then Noe.
就是这样 没有中间
That's it. No in-betweens.
然后 我
And I, uh...
我以前在瓦特殖民地开过一家病理学实验室
I used to run a pathology lab in the Watt Colonies.
搞什么鬼
What the shit, man?!
你说是她会打脸的
You said that she was gonna be doing the face punching!
现在我俩都说谎了 你不是那个达达
So now we both have lied. You are not that Dada.
你是那些人口中说的他的镜像版本
You're what these people call his Mirror.
你来自人族帝国
You came here from the Terran Empire,
然后你带来了天赐之物
and you brought the Godsend.
什么天赐之物
What's the Godsend?
我自己的军事委员会试图废黜我
My own war council tried to depose me.
你知道我是怎么说服元帅开口的吗
Do you know how I convinced the field marshal to talk?
我曾是个管理员
I was an administrator
在地球上的帝国武器设施工作
at an Imperial weapons facility on Terra.
是的
Uh, yeah.
天赐之物被存放在我管理的设施中
The Godsend was stored at my facility.
大多数人认为这只是一个传说 但我知道这是真的
Most thought it was a legend, but I knew it was real.
所以你想卖掉它
So you tried to sell it.
是 是的
Yeah, yeah.
我想靠得来的收益安静地生活在这里
I wanted to live here quietly on its proceeds.
你是怎么来到我们的宇宙的
How did you get to our universe?
有一个离子风暴
There was an ion storm.
实际上是两个
Two of them, actually.
当它们汇合时 就像时钟的钟摆一样
And when they converged, which they do like clockwork,
它们在帝国的边缘撕开了什么东西
they ripped something open on the fringes of the Empire--
他们称之为 一个异像 但这实际上是一条通道
an anomaly, they called it-- but it was a passageway
从人族帝国通往这里
to get to this place from the Terran Empire.
从你们的新月星云穿出
Comes out through your Crescent Nebula.
很少有人知道 至少现在是
Few know about it. For now.
但它四小时后会重新开放
But it'll open again in four hours.
那是我要去见买家的时间
That's when I was supposed to be meeting my buyer.
你知道那武器的作用吗
Are you aware of what that weapon does?
人族帝国已经快耗尽了资源
The Terran Empire's burned through its resources.
物资严重匮乏
There's famine.
整个生态系统正在崩溃
Entire ecologies are collapsing.
他们需要寻找新的土地
They need to find a new territory
来征服以及压榨
to conquer and strip-mine.
当他们意识到他们的超级武器不见了
When they realize that their superweapon is gone,
他们会找到那个通道--
they're gonna find that passageway--
你知道他们会的 而且他们会过来
you know they will-- and they'll come
烧光所有他们接触过的东西 奴役活着的人
and they'll burn everything they touch and enslave the rest,
因为你的帝国就是这么做的 “陛下”
because that's what the Empire does, Majesty.
他们把你的套路都学会了
They learned well from you.
还有谁想要它？
Who else wants it?
我不知道 伙计
I-I don't know, man.
我收到了一个报价 钱是真的
I got an offer. The money was real.
有人偷走了我们的神之使（神之死）
Someone stole the Godsend from us.
- 谁？- 不知道
- Who was he? - DADA NOE: No idea.
无论谁闯入我的地盘 无论谁偷了那件武器
Whoever broke into my room, whoever stole that weapon,
他们知道些东西 因为得到了
they know what they know because they learned it
你们中的某一个人提供的情报
from one of you.
紧急传送
Emergency transporter.
这可真棒
Well, this is great.
更棒了
Oh, even better.
那是飞船吗？船没了？
ZEPH: Is that... is that the ship? Is the ship gone?
我还挺喜欢那艘船的
I liked that ship.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
被破坏了
Sabotage.
什么？
What?
偷走神之使（神之死）的人有一个同伙
GEORGIOU: Whoever stole the Godsend had a partner.
在我们几个之中
It was someone here.
这意味着我们中的一个是内鬼
Which means one of us is a mole.
- 可能是你 - 可能是你
- Could be you. - Could be you.
如果是我
If it were me,
我早把你们都杀了
I would have murdered all of you already.
听着 老大 如果有内鬼 你应该知道不是我
Look, boss, if there's a mole, you know it's not me.
虽然我这话自己听起来也很像内奸
I mean, that sounds pretty moley to me.
我也迷糊了
I don't know.
我们已经一起执行了大约十次行动
QUASI: We've been on like ten ops together.
是 但我仍然不知道你长什么样 对吧？
Yeah, and I still don't even know what you look like, do I?
没有人知道02长什么样子
No one knows what a Chameloid looks like.
- 你可以变成任何你想要的东西 - 法兹呢？
- You might change into anything you want. - What about Fuzz, huh?
- 他的体型与其他人都不在一个尺度上 - 转移注意力？
- He exists on a whole other scale than anybody else. - Mm, deflecting?
我的妻子即将产下我们的第一窝卵囊
My wife is about to lay our first litter of egg sacs.
我还有19万只幼崽正在路上……
- No, I have 190,000 hatchlings on the way... - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- ...我希望他们活下去 - 好吧 听着
- ...and I want them to live. - Well, look,
你可以在我们中的任何人找到动机
you could find a motive for any of us.
也可能是你们中任何两个的组合
Or it could be a combination of any of you.
你知道 就像泽夫和法兹或者.
You know, like-like Zeph and-and Fuzz or...
你漏掉了梅勒
You are spinning out without Melle.
你无法做出选择
You cannot land on a choice.
也许你试图往我脑子里灌输这个观点 是因为你是内鬼
Maybe you're putting that in my head because you're the mole.
会不会是加勒特？她是新来的
Huh? How about Garrett? She's new.
她不在乎我们
She doesn't care about us.
我是星际舰队
I'm Starfleet.
还有没有人像我一样感受到一阵英雄主义的风
Whoa. Anyone else feel that heroic breeze right there
弄乱了她的斗篷？
ruffling her cape?
好吧 那里有一艘旧船
Okay, there's an old ship out there,
一艘旧垃圾驳船
an old garbage scow.
是的 我发现它的时候你在上面
Yeah, I found it when you were up there
审问金属脑袋
interrogating metal head.
一定已经很多年没有人驾驶过它了
Must be years since anyone flew it,
但我认为我们可以修复它
but I think we can work with it
追捕拿走神之使（神之死）的人
to go after whoever took the Godsend.
我没那么不喜欢你了
Mm. I dislike you less.
如果我想有人喜欢我 我就会养一只狗
If I wanted someone to like me, I'd get a dog.
我喜欢秩序
I like order.
我喜欢预测和结论
I like prediction and conclusion.
那你就选错了团队 因为我们面对的是 内鬼
Then you're on the wrong team because we've got mole,
被困在一颗死去的星球
stranded on a dead planet,
与外界没有沟通方式
no communication with the outside,
以及不到四个小时之后人族将得到神之使（神之死）
and less than four hours before the Terrans get the Godsend
并在银河系的任何地方使用它
and use it anywhere in the galaxy.
说到这里 夸西 天线阵列怎么样了？
Speaking of which, Quas, what about the antenna array?
这个嘛...
Uh, well...
嗯 它已经过时了几十年了
Well, it's a couple decades out of date.
我们修复它 告诉31区即将发生的事情
We get it up and running, then we tell 31 what's coming.
我们一起工作
We work together.
- 每个人都不要离开视线 - 好的
- Everyone stays in sight. - QUASI: Yeah.
只是...
Just...
走吧
Let's go.
那个想法泡汤了
QUASI: Well, there goes that idea.
我们的小内鬼真的很忙
Our little mole has been really busy.
扯断了所有线路
Ripped up all the wiring.
分两个队 我会带一个进入树林
Two teams. I'll lead one into the woods.
三个人 看看我们是否能挽救那艘小艇
Three to see if we can salvage that scow.
你和其他人一起留在这里
You stay here with the others
并尝试修复天线阵列
and try and fix the antenna array.
为什么她现在在对我们发号施令？
Why is she giving us orders now?
因为我让她发号施令的
Because I'm letting her
我很确定她不是内奸
and I'm pretty certain she's not the mole.
你不会把赌注押在一匹名叫“很确定”的马上
You wouldn't bet on a horse named Pretty Certain.
夸西、法兹 你们马上和乔久一起去船
Quas, Fuzz, you get to the scow right away with Georgiou.
泽夫和加勒特 你们跟我待在这
Zeph and Garrett, you stay here with me.
我们会搞定天线阵列的
We'll take care of the antenna array.
请解释一下
Uh, I'm sorry.
我是应该出去
I'm supposed to go out into the woods
和两个想杀我的人一起进入树林？
with two people who want to kill me?
保持在彼此的视线之内 别死了就行
Just stay in sight of each other and don't get dead.
好吗？
Okay?
好吧 谢谢 队长
QUASI: Yep, thanks, Cap.
我的意思是 50%的概率 他们中的一个人想杀我
I mean, just fifty-fifty shot one of them wants to kill me,
- 然后是25%的... - 夸西 赶紧出去吧
- and then 25%... - Quas, just get your ass out there.
我也爱你 队长
I love you, too, Cap.
一切就绪 遵命
- ALOK: All righty. - QUASI: Aye, aye.
这艘旧船上的内部电路
QUASI: The internal circuitry on this old scow
状态仍然不错
is still in decent shape.
-我看到的一切都应该能用
- Everything I'm seeing should work.
所以我们正在追的东西 神之使（神之死）
So this thing we're chasing, the Godsend,
你的工程师 他们安装保险没有？
your engineers, did they install a fail-safe?
我们可以远程禁用它吗？
Can we disable it remotely?
没有这种保险 我不会允许的
There is no fail-safe. I wouldn't allow it.
不愧是你
How very on-brand for you.
我可以再问你一个问题吗？
Can I ask you one more question?
我就只再问你一个问题
I'm just gonna ask you one more question.
所以你把神之使带到了这个世界上
So you brought the Godsend into the world
是为了蒸发数万亿生命
to vaporize quadrillions of lives.
就从来没有想过这有点 太过火了？
Never thought that was a little, you know, much?
我下令销毁它
I ordered it destroyed.
有人把它藏起来了 你自己的人背叛了你
And someone hid it. Your own people betrayed you.
你们的企业文化就是彻头彻尾的狗屎
Well, your corporate culture was straight-up shit.
而且你没有回答我的问题
And you didn't answer my question.
线圈没了
The asymptote coil is gone.
一定是有人把它拾走了
Someone must have scavenged it for the terbium.
好吧 再找一个 这个东西应该能飞
Well, find another one, this thing should fly.
- 也许是货箱 - 别 别
- Maybe the cargo hull. - Huh. Oh, no, no.
每个人都待在一起 好吗？
Everyone stays together, all right?
降低你杀死我们的可能性
Limits the possibilities of you killing us.
我们去货舱吧
Let's go to the cargo hold, please.
你不来吗？
Aren't you coming?
来 我可太高兴了
Yes. I couldn't be more excited.
当然 我可以在那里帮助你
ZEPH: Yeah, I could help you down there, of course,
但考虑到 控制
but considering how, you know, control
是你整个身份的核心
is central to your entire identity
而事实上我不擅长控制
and the fact that I'm just not good at it,
我就站在这里 为了我们的关系
I'm just gonna stand here and honor our relationship
- 什么也不做 - 还真热心呢
- by doing absolutely nothing. - ALOK: Helpful.
这被称为激进的自我接受
It's called radical self-acceptance.
- 从你身上演进而来 - 谢谢你
- Evolved of you. - Well, thank you.
所以说 你能修好它吗？
So, can you fix it?
我甚至不确定它是否坏了 只是少了个零件罢了
I'm not even sure it's broken. It's just missing a part.
看 这个--这根撕裂的电线看起来很戏剧性
Look, this-this torn wiring looks dramatic,
但该设备内置了冗余
but this equipment has redundancy built in.
有一个简单的解决办法
There's an easy work-around.
唯一问题是 有人取出了θ节点
Except somebody ripped out the theta junction.
除此之外 这个东西应该可以用
Other than that, this thing should work.
好吧 也许我们的内鬼得到了它
Okay, well, maybe our mole has it.
- 加勒特？- 咋了
- Garrett? - Yeah.
泽夫
Zeph.
泽夫在哪里？
Where is Zeph?
泽夫 进来
Zeph, come in.
泽夫 你收到吗？
Zeph, do you copy?
泽夫
Zeph.
加勒特 是你吗？
Garrett, was that you?
加勒特 那到底是什么？
Garrett, what the hell was that?
有人刚刚激活了天线阵列
Someone just activated the antenna array.
该死
Damn it.
发生了什么？
What's happening?
加勒特 情况简报
Garrett, sitrep.
越来越棒了
This is going to be good.
中尉 收到了吗？完毕
Lieutenant, do you copy? Over.
安全
Clear.
这里什么都没有
Nothing here.
怎么会有人用这个来发出信号呢？
How could someone have used this to send out a signal?
不可能 它少了一个部件
Impossible. It's missing a part.
有人把它打成了筛子
And someone shot it to hell.
我听到有人在跑
I heard someone running.
泽夫一定是把θ节点放回去了
Zeph must have put the theta junction back in.
使用阵列后 射击阵列
Then shot it after he used the array.
所以他一定是在擅离职守后绕回来的
So he must have circled back after he went AWOL.
泽夫来这个星球来阻碍我们
Zeph came down to this planet to sabotage us.
现在我们被困住了
And now that we're stranded,
他给同谋发了信息
he sent a message to whoever he's working with.
他会潜伏直到撤离的船抵达
And he'll lay low until his ride gets here,
然后逃之夭夭
and then he's long gone.
那我们得先找到他
Then we need to find him first.
观察者 收到吗？
Observer, do you copy?
拜托 突袭者一号 我什么时候收不到？
GARRETT: Please, Raider One, when do I not copy?
真好笑 情况如何？
That's funny. Status?
我收到了很多干扰
GARRETT: I'm picking up a lot of interference,
但三录仪显示 泽夫的生命信号
but the tricorder shows Zeph's biosignature
就在这个区域 完毕
was just in this sector. Over.
收到 全体都有 保持低调 保持队形
Copy. Stay low and tight, people.
你服务的那个军阀 吉里 她怎么了？
The warlord you served, Giri, what happened to her?
她死了 死于生前最爱的事
She died like she lived.
你知道我说的什么
By that, you know what I mean.
她很幸运
She was lucky.
她并没染上良心这种东西
She wasn't infected with a conscience.
染？-是的
- Infected? - Yeah.
怪物只能是怪物
A monster can only be a monster.
一个会悔恨的怪物是没用的
A monster with regrets is useless.
嗯 所以这就是你躲起来的原因
Mm. So that's why you were hiding
在一个不毛之地的酒吧
in a bar at the ass end of nowhere.
也许这就是你和31区的人合作的原因
Maybe it's why you're working with 31.
把你的前科抹掉
To wipe your slate clean.
像我们这样的人总是要付出代价的
ALOK: There's always a price to pay for people like us.
如果你不同意 你就不会在这里
You wouldn't be here if you didn't agree.
所以这就是你选择我的原因
Oh, so that's why you chose me.
你认为我是一个有足够感情的怪物 可以被控制
You think I'm a monster who feels enough to be controlled
但仍在做真正肮脏的工作
but still do the real dirty work.
不 我认为你想要回神之使 因为你知道
No, I think you want the Godsend back because you know
这是你救赎自己的唯一机会
it's your one chance to redeem yourself
为你所做的一切付出代价
for all the shit you've done.
我想要回它 只因为它是我的
I want the Godsend back because it's mine.
泽夫的外骨骼正在渗漏
Ah. Zeph's exoskeleton is leaking.
是的 更多
Yep, more.
这边
GEORGIOU: This way.
暴跳 夹子
Blip, Clip,
紧握
Grip,
小儿麻痹症 流感
Polio, Influensina,
- 牛痘 - 你在说什么？
- Cowpox... - What are you saying?
我正在背诵我即将孵化的幼崽的名字
I'm reciting the names of me hatchlings.
因为你们中的一个要谋杀我
Since one of you is going to murder me,
我永远不会见到他们 但至少我可以向他们致敬
I'm never gonna meet them, but at least I can honor them
一个接一个
one by one.
旅行
Trip,
旅行二世
Trip 2,
扁桃体炎 克里米亚-刚果出血热……
Tonsilyitis, Crimean-Congo Hemorrhagic Fever...
你要哭着说出19万孩子的名字吗？
Are you gonna sob out 190,000 names?
你怎么能这么冷漠 如此无情？
How can you be so cold and insensitive?
他有可能记录下了发生的一切吗？
Might he have recorded what happened?
当然
QUASI: Sure.
只是这段视频很可能和他一起被谋杀了
Except the footage was probably murdered along with him.
我们可以将其中一个三录仪连接到他的西装上
ALOK: We could connect one of the tricorders to his suit.
无论剩下什么 我们都会知道是谁干的
Whatever data is left, we'll know who did this.
你这么说就好像我们都是嫌疑人一样
QUASI: You say that like we're all suspects.
我们不是 好吗？
We're not. All right?
这一切发生时我和法兹都在船上
Fuzz, me and her were in the scow when all this happened--
每个人都留在别人的视线范围内
everyone in sight of everyone else.
没人去任何地方 对吧？
And nobody went anywhere, right?
- 对的 - 嗯
- Right. - GEORGIOU: Hmm.
这不是泽夫的
Oh, this is not Zeph's.
深褐色头发 25厘米
Brunette. 25 centimeters.
这太疯狂了
This is insane.
别再坐立不安了
Stop fidgeting.
我已经和泽夫近距离接触了一周了
I've been in close quarters with Zeph for a week.
好吧 所以你喜欢赛博格
Okay, so you're into mecha boom-boom.
很多人类都是 不必害羞
Lots of humans are. No shame.
嗯 那是不可能的
Well, that's impossible.
加勒特中尉
ALOK: Lieutenant Garrett,
为什么你的指甲底下有泽夫的血？
why is Zeph's blood underneath your fingernails?
加勒特中尉
GEORGIOU: Lieutenant Garrett,
在泽夫的尸体上发现了你的证据
evidence from you was found on Zeph's body,
泽夫尸体上的证据也在你身上发现了
and evidence from Zeph's body was found on you.
不太星际舰队
Not very Starfleet.
哦 我非常星际舰队
Oh, I am very Starfleet.
你知道我没有这么做
And you know I didn't do this.
你只是害怕任何有道德准则的人
You are just terrified of anyone with a moral compass.
在那颗纯洁的小心灵的深处
And deep down in that pure little heart,
你实际上是一个混乱的妖精 对吧？
you're actually a chaos goblin, aren't you?
- 我知道你是这样的 小天使 - 别这么叫我
- I know you have it in you, angel. - Don't call me that.
星际舰队嗅出了你
Starfleet sniffed you out
并把你放在一个最有用的地方
and put you in a place where you'd be most useful.
31区正是违反规则的军官该来的地方
Section 31 is just the place for officers who bend the rules,
在他们打破规则之前 永远不会完全打破规则
never quite break them until they do.
你很适合这里
And you fit right in here.
你想怎么折磨我都可以
GARRETT: You can torture me all you want.
你永远不会让我成为杀人犯
You will never make me a murderer.
不是
ALOK: No.
卡西：我们拿到录像了！
QUASI: We've got footage!
住手
Stop!
停止播放!
这是我的装甲
This is my suit.
我即是装甲！
I am the suit!
装甲就是我！
The suit is me!
等一下
One second.
我们是你的朋友 我们是你的朋友
We were your friends. We were your friends.
你杀不了我
You can't kill me.
-泽夫 不 -你不能杀...
- QUASI: Zeph, no. - You can't kill...
泽夫杀了自己？
QUASI: Zeph killed himself?
他为什么要这么做？
Why would he do that?
抱歉让您失望了 陛下
Sorry to disappoint you, Your Majesty.
这一切根本说不通
Look, none of this is making any sense.
是啊 非常之不合理
No, none of it makes a lick of sense.
他为什么要这样做呢
Why would he do this? Uh...
给我几分钟 我们没时间了
- Give me a couple minutes to... - We don't have minutes.
就几秒钟
Well, then give me a couple seconds, then.
呃
Uh...
可能是你干的 也可能是你干的
- Could be you. - GEORGIOU: Could be you.
而且我连你长什么样都不知道
And I still don't even know what you look like.
你可以变形
You could change into anything you want.
她是新来的 她才不在乎我们
She's new. She doesn't care about us.
我是星际舰队的 哇哦
- I'm Starfleet. - Whoa.
你们提到那套装备时
When you are talking about the suit,
就会想起泽夫
you're talking about Zeph.
这可不是法兹
This isn't Fuzz.
那个瓦肯人只是一个机器
The Vulcan's just a machine, you know.
我在里面呢
I'm inside.
奇耻大辱
Scale-shamer!
你绝对想不到我能钻进多小的缝隙
You wouldn't believe the tiny spots I can get into.
人体的内部系统
For example, the inner workings of body modifications.
有个自动驾驶程序
There's an autopilot.
这是唯一合理的解释
That's the only thing that makes sense.
你给瓦肯机器设了自动驾驶程序
You set the Vulcan machine on autopilot.
所以它的反应才那么古怪
That's why its responses were so strange.
你来不来 当然
- Aren't you coming? - Yes.
你钻进泽夫的外骨骼，控制了他的装备
You flew into Zeph's exoskeleton.
一旦你进入以后
And once you were inside...
有人把西塔接口拆掉了
Somebody ripped out  the theta junction.
加勒特 泽夫呢
Garrett, where's Zeph?
然后你接管了泽夫的装备
Then you took control of Zeph's suit.
当别人在找他的时候
While the others were out looking for him,
你让他溜回了通讯阵列
you made him sneak back into the antenna array
然后发送了那些信息
and send those messages.
不要这么做
Don't do this to them!
我们是你的朋友啊
We were your friends.
然后你销毁了所有证据
Then you destroyed the evidence.
还杀掉了泽夫
And you killed Zeph.
然后你把这一切嫁祸给加勒特
And then you planted the evidence on Garrett here.
举起手来 法兹
Hands up, Fuzz.
倒了血霉了
Oh, shite and ever shite.
等等等等 你们还要信她的鬼话吗 阿罗克
Whoa. You're honestly gonna believe what she says, Alok?
夸西 经历这么多你还相信她吗
Quasi, after everything we've been through?
我能先说一句吗
C-Can I just say one thing first?
我还能接入泽夫的外骨骼
I'm still hacked into Zeph's exoskeleton.
快点
Come on!
说好的“不抛弃任何人”呢
What happened to "no crew member left behind"?
快一点啊
Come on, come on!
靠近他们
Get us closer.
♪
逮到你了
I got you. I got you.
小菜一碟  该死
- Nice and easy. - ALOK: Damn.
你很关注黑市的动向
You keep tabs on the black market, hmm?
你就是在那听说天赐之物的消息的
And that's where you heard about the Godsend.
你怎么会在乎
Why do you care?
你杀了你的家人
You killed your family.
再多点人算什么呢
What's a few billion more people, huh?
他在哪 你在和谁说话
Where is it? And who are you working with?
你登上了王位
You took your crown while they died in agony
他们却死在你的脚边
not ten feet away.
你奴役了你唯一的朋友
You condemned your only friend to slavery,
然后居然向他表示善意
and then you had the balls to offer him kindness at the end?
你怎么会知道
How could you know that?
你终于发现了
Glad you're catching on.
他把你耍了 皇帝陛下
He played you, Emperor.
San还活着
San's alive.
不可能
It's not possible.
绝对不可能 怎么一回事
That's not possible. How?
他在培养对毒药的抗药性
He built up an immunity from that poison, you know.
每次只是很小的剂量
Teeny tiny doses over time.
看样子是小混蛋又赢了一次
Once again, small shite for the win, mama.
他在哪
Where is he?!
在出其不意的地方
He's gonna put on quite the show.
你制造了神赐之物
You built the Godsend.
你让它成为了怪物
You made this monster.
全是因为你
This is all you.
小心点可以吗
Be careful, all right?
我说了小心点
I said be careful.
我还在船里呢
I have to get around in that.
你都能买得起一百多艘了还在乎这一艘
You can afford a hundred of them now.
太好了
FUZZ: Oh, great.
我要激活一个
I'd settle for one that works.
所以就是这个
So that's it?
无敌的神赐之物
The almighty Godsend.
当你做上皇帝了
When you're emperor,
给它起一个没那么奇怪的名字
maybe start by naming it something less confusing.
当传送门打开时
Once that passageway opens up,
他会联系人族 他们会穿过传送门
he contacts the Terrans, they come through.
然后他们会引爆这里
They're detonating it here.
他成了帝国的宠儿
And he'd be the darling of the Empire.
联邦陷入混乱
So he throws the Federation into chaos...
星际舰队自顾不暇
Starfleet will start scrambling.
入侵的完美时机
Perfect time to invade.
你创造了它
You gave birth to this thing.
我们要怎么阻止他 我们不
- How do we stop it? - GEORGIOU: We don't.
我们被困在这 追不上他
We're trapped here, so we can't follow him.
通讯天线坏了 我们也无法警告任何人
The antenna's destroyed, so we can't warn anybody.
胡扯
That is bullshit.
你肯定有更好的办法 没有
- You can do better than that. - I can't.
天赐之物是我
The Godsend is me.
我无法战胜我自己
I'm the only one I could never defeat.
过去总是缠着你不放
The past always catches up with you.
不是吗
Right?
但并不一定每次都赢
Doesn't mean it always wins.
每个安全屋都有备用计划
Every safe house, I have a backup plan.
把那艘垃圾船修好
We'll get that scow running.
老大 那家伙飞不起来的
Boss, the scow won't fly.
没有渐进线圈就不可能
Not without an asymptote coil.
我们有一个
ALOK: We have one.
我们会追上San的
We'll catch up with San.
我们要阻止他联系人族
We'll make sure he can't contact the Terrans.
你把线圈扯掉了
You ripped out the coil.
有内奸在 我可没法什么都告诉你
Couldn't tell you while a mole was still running around.
你个混蛋
Asshole.
夸西 去帮她一下
Okay, Quas, give her a rip.
还是只有一个脉冲引擎
Still just one pulse.
来活了朋友们
And we're in business.
我们只有不到三十分钟时间
Okay, team, we have less than 30 minutes.
夸西 设定航线前往新月星云
Quas, set a course for the Crescent Nebula.
路上将会非常颠簸
All right, this is gonna be bumpy and bad.
我推测san的星舰会有武器
I'm assuming San's ship will be armed.
废话 所有人族星舰都是战舰
Yeah, every Terran ship's armed.
我们有光子炮 鱼类
He'll have proton cannons, torpedoes,
还有一个大垃圾袋
and we are a garbage barge.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
因为我想不出来还有什么更糟的情况了
Because I can't imagine things getting much worse.
出发
Let's go.
这东西可以在牵引立场中飞行
So, this thing flies around in the middle of a tractor field.
人们向太空里面扔垃圾
People jettison their garbage into space,
然后这种驳船会拖着垃圾
and the scow flies around and drags the trash
在力场中飞行
along with the field.
一旦牵引立场充能完毕
Once the tractor field is full,
就会把垃圾甩进星云里
it dumps the trash in the Nebula
垃圾会在辐射里分解掉
where it disintegrates in the radiation.
我就是想确认一下
I just want to be clear.
你是想说我们最有可能用的上的武器
You're saying that our best potential weapon is
是垃圾回收光束
a beam for collecting garbage?
是 太棒了
- Yes. - Great.
你在那指手画脚帮不上一点忙
Hey, being judgy never helped anything.
你要去哪 轮机室
- Where are you going? - Engineering.
如果那是我们唯一的武器
If that's our only weapon,
我要把所有的能量都导入那里
I'll redirect all power to the tractor beams.
这计划确实不错呢
That's actually a good plan.
就位了
We're in position.
传送门很快就会打开
The passageway will open soon.
你知道我在这一切结束后想干什么吗
Do you know what I want when this is all over?
这么大的一块空域
Just a big space, you know,
让我和我的小家伙们到处乱飞
for me hatchlings to tunnel and fly around and...
你想干什么
What do you want?
我要菲利帕乔久永远沉浸在她的失败之中
I want Philippa Georgiou to marinate in her own defeat.
我懂你们的
I get you guys are all "eternal nemesis,
你们都是那种复仇永恒论的人
sexy evil tension" and stuff, but...
警报
Alert.
有飞船靠近
Incoming vessel.
检测到碰撞轨迹
Collision trajectory detected.
她确实能把那玩意飞起来
Of course she got it off the ground.
我建议我们用鱼雷
I say we should use the torpedoes.
他发现我们了
They've picked us up.
光子鱼雷来袭
Photon torpedo incoming.
倒计时 五 四 我们需要进行规避机动
- Impact in five, four...- Really want to take evasive action right now!
三 二 一  夸西 保持航线 护盾设置最大
- ...three, two, one. - Quas, hold the course. Put everything in our shields.
她为什么不改变航线呢
Why isn't she changing course?
我看起来像是投机取巧的吗
Do I look like a fortune teller?
我们有足够的能量牵引他们吗
Do we have enough juice to drag them with the tractor beam yet?
有 但我们没法承受下一次直接命中的鱼雷了
Yeah, but we can't take another direct hit.
鱼雷来袭 五 四 三
Incoming torpedo in five, four...
保持稳定 我们马上到了  三 二 一
- Keep it steady. We're almost there... - ...three, two, one.
就现在
Now.
导航控制暂停
Navigation control suspended.
他们在干什么 想拖死我们
What are they gonna do, drag us to death?
她在阻止我和帝国取得联系
She's trying to stop me from reaching the Empire.
哦
Oh.
大家感觉如何
How's everybody feeling about this?
这是唯一的办法了
It's the only way.
这办法有用
This can work.
辐射会削减他们的护盾
The radiation will wear down their shields.
是啊 但是辐射也会影响我们
Yeah, the thing is, the radiation hits us, too.
目标锁定失效
Target lock malfunction.
鱼类无法锁定 加农炮也掉线了
I can't get torpedo lock. Cannons offline.
桑?
San?
san
San.
桑!
San!
辐射等级已致命
Radiation levels critical.
护盾失效 重复 护盾失效
Shields are down. I repeat, shields are down!
他的呢
And San's?
12% 还在迅速下降
His are at 12% and falling fast.
等离子风暴来袭
Plasma incoming!
如果我们被卷入这样的爆炸里
We get caught with a burst like that,
我们就完了
and we're done.
这就是混乱 加勒特
This is chaos, Garrett.
你喜欢混乱没错吧
You know you love it, hmm?
直面它 和它聊聊
Maybe let it in, make out with it a little.
这就是星际舰队为何要你来这里的原因
It's why Starfleet put you here.
混乱是我最好的朋友
Chaos is my friend with benefits.
就是这样 越混乱越好
Yeah, Garrett, let's get messy.
怎么样 当然
- Hmm? - Okay.
你负责这个 夸西 没问题
- You got this, Quas. - Uh-huh.
准备好了吗
You ready?
san的护盾还有4%
San's shields are at four percent.
2%
Two now.
护盾消失了
His shields are down.
可以出发了
Good to go.
菲利帕
Philippa!
我们这次
This contest only ends
不死不休
when one of us is dead!
自毁程序已启动
Detonation sequence activating.
See, the Nanokins, we don't need the Federation.
你看，我们纳米人不需要星际联邦
We never have.
从来如此
We ruled before you behemoths found us,
早在你们这些庞然大物找到我们之前我们就在统治了
and we will rule again after you're gone.
在你们死后，我们会再次统治
Guess who survives very large explosions.
猜猜谁会在大爆炸中存活下来
Very small things.
小东西们
Now, if you'll excuse me, I need to cut our ship loose.
现在 请原谅 我得把船脱离出去
Sorry if your friends die in the process.
如果你的朋友在这个过程里死了那真是抱歉
No, I'm joking.
不 我在开玩笑
I can't wait to kill them.
我等不及要杀死他们了
So long, you big lumps of shite!
再见了 你个巨大狗屎
Who's flying that?
谁在驾驶那艘飞船
Uh, according to the sensors, one tiny life-form on board,
根据传感器 上面有一个微型生命
and it's heading right for us.
它在朝我们飞过来
Plot missile lock.
导弹锁定
We have trash, all right? Just trash.
我们只有垃圾 明白吗 只有垃圾
But one.
但合二为一
San.
圣
Awaiting biosignature confirmation.
等待确认生物签名
I've got Fuzz's shuttle.
我追踪到法兹的穿梭艇了
He's heading back to San's ship.
他要回到圣的船上
- We're barely keeping up. - Stay on him.
-我们只能勉强跟上 -跟住他
Uh, we don't have any weapons.
我们没有任何武器
We have a payload bay full of trash.
我们有一个载满垃圾的有效载荷舱
Do not lose that shuttle.
不要跟丢那个穿梭艇
Okay.
好吧
I was nothing!
我曾经什么都不是
That boy was soft, weak.
那个男孩软弱无力
But all those years under your heel taught me who I am now.
但在你脚下服侍的这些年教出了现在的我
The Empire's coming through that portal.
帝国正通过传送门过来
My Empire!
我的帝国
And we will reign over this universe
我们将统治这个宇宙
with righteous mercy, not like you!
用公正又仁慈的手段 不像你
There are no benevolent dictators, San.
没有仁慈的独裁者 圣
You taught me that.
你教会我的
We can come back from this.
我们还能回头
We can start over.
我们可以重新开始
Oh, I love chaos.
哦 我爱混乱
Chaos is my jam.
混乱是我的菜
I love chaos. I love chaos.
我爱混乱 我爱混乱
Garrett, what the hell are you doing down there?
加勒特 你在那下面干啥呢
Quasi, I am a trained Starfleet officer
夸西 我是个训练有素的星际舰队军官
who fully intends on living long enough to be captain one day.
想活得到能当上舰长的那一天
You got to trust me, okay?
你得相信我 好吗
Hi there.
你好呀
I'm so glad you found me.
真高兴你找到了我
What'd you just say?
你刚才说了什么
Uh... uh...
呃 呃
It's a toy.
这是个玩具
Looks like it came from a Droom planet.
看起来它来自一个德鲁姆行星
Shall we do something fun together?
来一起找点乐子怎么样
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
喔 喔 喔 喔
You okay down there, Starfleet?
你还好吗 星际舰队的
Whoa.
喔
Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on. Yes.
哦 拜托 拜托 拜托 拜托 太好了
Oh, we do not let Droom tech into the Federation
我们不允许德鲁姆科技进入联邦
because they use Terrenium as a power source.
因为他们用地金（或者特瑞金？）作为电源
Oh, you're gonna blow us up, aren't you?
你要炸飞我们 是吗
You better hope that this ship's hull
你最好希望这艘船的船体
is reinforced with Tomohite.
用特莫矿加固过
I am a science officer.
我是一名科学官
And science is just controlled chaos.
科学就是受控的混乱
Whoa, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos, chaos!
混乱 混乱 混乱 混乱 混乱
Ah, come on.
得了吧
Get up, you stupid robot.
起来 你个愚蠢的机器人
No. No.
不 不
No!
不
Stay in front of Fuzz's ship so we can open the payload bay.
待在法兹的飞船前 这样我们可以打开有效载荷舱
Uh, yeah.
呃 好
About that.
关于那个
- Uh, thing is... - Quasi, there's about to be a very large explosion.
-是这样 -夸西 马上要有场非常大的爆炸
This console's in a language I don't know.
这个控制台的语言我看不懂
I can decipher some of it.
我能破译其中一些
I just have to break it down to morphemes
我只需要把它分解成语素
- and, you know... - Large explosion impending.
-然后 你知道 -大爆炸要来了
Either of these two buttons could open the cargo bay.
这两个按钮都有可能打开货舱
Okay, so push them both.
好的 那就都按了
Either of these two buttons could also
这两个按钮也都有可能
initiate a self-destruct protocol.
启动自毁程序
- We're gonna blow up anyway. - Uh-huh.
-我们怎样都会被炸飞 -嗯哼
- Um, uh.. Huh? - Quasi. Quasi, look at me.
-嗯 呃 嗯 -夸西 夸西 看着我
You just need to make a call.
你只需要做个决定
You know what to do.
你知道该做什么
- Okay. - Okay.
-好 -好
Uh...
呃
We can be friends forever...
我们可以永远做朋友
Do you want to hear something funny?
你想听点有趣的事吗
I'm on autopilot.
我在自动驾驶状态
What the hell?
什么鬼
We're all gonna die.
我们都要死了
No!
不
It's wonderful just to be with you.
能和你在一起真是太好了
- Whoo! - Whoa!
-喔 -哇
Yes!
-好
Die now.
死吧
Go tell your family how much you've changed.
去告诉你的家人你变了多少
San.
圣
No. No.
不 不
No.
不
San.
圣
This is not what I want.
这不是我想要的
Please.
求你了
- I love you. - I love you.
-我爱你 -我爱你
San.
圣
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
真的对不起
You-you-you were right.
你 你是对的
I still needed you.
我仍然需要你
I always needed...
我一直需要
To show me who I am, even now.
让我明白我是谁 即便是现在
Now.
现在
M-M... My emperor.
我的皇帝
My love.
我的爱人
No.
不
We are one.
我们是一体
Forever.
直到永远
Ion storm convergence imminent.
离子风暴合流迫近
Passageway is opening.
通道正在打开
Biosignature confirmed.
生物签名确认
Detonation in 60 seconds.
六十秒后引爆
Computer, target lock on the passageway.
电脑 目标锁定通道
Target lock confirmed.
目标锁定确认
If you could go back,
如果你能回去
and you were kneeling in front of Giri,
跪在吉里面前
would you kill her?
你能杀了她吗
Would you put a stop to all the suffering and smoke forever,
你能否永远结束所有的痛苦和硝烟
even if it meant that you had to die?
就算这意味着你必须死
Yes.
我会的
Then I'm glad I knew you, Alok Sahar.
那么我很高兴认识了你 阿洛克·萨哈
Detonation in 30 seconds.
三十秒后引爆
Passageway is open.
通道打开
Sensors show they've activated impulse engines.
传感器显示他们启动了脉冲引擎
What?
什么
- Yeah. - You need to transport them back.
-没错 -你得把他们传送回来
- Yeah. Okay. - Now.
-好的 -现在
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
好的 好的 好的 好的
The storm's interfering. I can't lock on to them.
离子风暴在干扰我们 我无法锁定他们
Detonation in ten seconds.
十秒后引爆
Come on. Come on!
快点 快点
They're running out of time.
他们要没时间了
I'm trying.
我在努力
Detonation in five,
五秒后引爆
four, three,
四 三
two, one.
二 一
Lieutenant Garrett?
加勒特上尉
Rachel?
瑞秋
You all right?
你还好吗
- I'm okay. - Hmm? You here?
-我还好 -醒着呢
- Yeah. You're alive. - All right.
-嗯 你还活着 -好了
Yeah, Quasi got us out.
-是啊 夸西把我们救出来了
- There we go. There we are. - Thank you.
-好了 好了 -谢谢
Oh, you did it.
你做到了
Oh, we won.
我们赢了
- Oh. Grow up.
哦 成熟一点
Perkiness is disgusting.
这么活泼令人作呕
Yeah.
好吧
I hear you.
我知道了
It's happening.
就这样了
The passageway's collapsing.
通道在坍塌
（最终传讯 三个地球周之后）
There she is.
她在这儿
How was your debrief?
你的汇报如何
Oh, could've been worse.
够好的了
They made me an offer.
他们给我发了邀请
And?
然后呢
- I'm sitting on it.
我还在考虑
You?
你呢
Meh. Hmm.
还行 嗯
Hmm.
And how long did you think
你觉得你能用这招
you could fool me with this, hmm?
骗过我几次 嗯
- What gave it away? - Mm.
-哪里暴露了 -嗯
You still get nervous when I look at you.
我看着你时你还会紧张
Oh. Hey, C-Cap.
哦 嘿 舰长
Leave that poor man alone.
放过那个可怜的家伙吧
Virgil.
维吉尔
A round of elixirs for my friends.
给我的朋友上轮好酒
- Pleasure, Madame du Franc. - Mm-hmm.
-没问题 杜弗朗克女士 -嗯哼
Lieutenant Garrett.
加勒特上尉
They let you off the ship.
他们放你下船了
It's actually Lieutenant Commander Garrett now.
实际上 现在是加勒特上校了
- Oh. - Thank you very much.
-噢 -谢谢你
And if this unit is gonna be a permanent detail,
如果这个小队要成为常驻的
then you all definitely need oversight.
那你们绝对需要有人监督
I may slaughter you all at any moment.
我随时都可能杀掉你们所有人
Is that a deal-breaker?
这是个雷点吗
- Nah. - Whatevs.
-不算吧 -无所谓
It's not like you need a reason anyway.
反正你也不需要什么理由
It's true. You're a bad bitch.
这是真的 你就是个女王
- With the stare of death. - Oh, we get it.
-带着死亡凝视 -哦 我们懂
You're a terrifying, soulless murderer
你是个可怕的冷血杀手
who we can never truly trust.
我们永远也不能真心相信你
I love that for us.
我真为咱们感到高兴啊
Somebody's got to keep things lively.
总有人得活跃气氛
- Touché. - Yes, touché. - You make a point.
- 妙啊 -是啊 真妙啊 -你说得对
To us.
敬我们
This isn't poison, is it?
这不是毒药 对吧
And now that you have us all here,
现在你把我们都叫过来了
what next?
下一步是什么
Well, not quite all.
也不全在
Ladies and gent, stage left.
女士们先生们 舞台左侧
You got to be kidding me.
你一定在开玩笑吧
Oh, I'm not Fuzz.
哦 我不是法兹
Section 31 bought
三十一区从黑市上
two of these conveyances on the black market.
买了两个这种运输工具
Name's Wisp. I'm his wife.
我叫薇丝 是他的妻子
And I'm here for when we catch up with
我来是为了抓到那个
that lying, double-dealing son of a bitch.
满嘴扯谎 两面三刀的婊子
Uh, well, we blew up his ship, ma'am.
呃 我们把他的船炸了 女士
- Uh, Mrs. Fuzz. - Oh, honey.
- 呃 法兹夫人 -哦 亲爱的
Little things sometimes survive big explosions.
小东西有时能从大爆炸中生还
And when we find him, I have questions.
等我们找到他 我要问他点事
- Now, what are we talking about? - I'm glad you asked.
- 现在 我们在聊什么 -很高兴你问了
I was just letting the team know.
我正要让小队知道
Control has a job for us.
上级给我们发了活
My better judgment has been
我的理智已经向我
screaming at me for two days now.
尖叫整整两天了
It keeps saying that you lot are gonna cost me my job.
它一直在说你们会让我丢掉工作
- We might. - She might.
-我们也许会 -她也许会
I told my judgment to shut up
我告诉我的理智闭嘴
and take a nap.
去睡一觉
'Cause we have work to do.
因为我们还有工作要做
Has anybody been to Turkana IV?
有人去过图尔卡纳四星吗
- Whew. - Wait.
-呼 -等等
Did you say Turkana or say Jur-Jurnana?
你说的是图尔卡纳还是朱尔娜娜
He thought "Your Mama IV."
他以为是“你妈四星”
Oh, Your Mama IV.
你妈四星
No.
不是